youdownload.com 2018-08-27

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy  
**   
**Logging IP Addresses**  
For each visitor to our web page, our web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or email address. IP addresses are logged and used by us for measuring usage.

**Collecting Email Addresses**  
We collect the email addresses of our recipients and senders for the purpose of logging and measuring usage. Plunder does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with non-affiliated companies.

**Certain Exceptional Disclosures**  
We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal processes.

**Use of Cookies**  
We uses cookies to store the preferences of users, only if they so choose.

**File Transfer Security**  
We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. Files stored for delivery are only accessible by us and through the clickable link generated for your recipient. All files stored for delivery are deleted when they expire.

**Third-Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third-Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

DoubleClick DART cookies We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

Effective Date: July 22, 2009
